Guide to the Yale College Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale College Grade Sheets, Fall 2001; Accession 2005-A-146
  - Chemical Engineering, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chemistry, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Child Study, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chinese, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Classics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cognitive Science, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - College Seminars, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Comparative Literature, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Computer Science, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Czech, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Devane, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Directive Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Divinity, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Drama School, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - East Asian Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Economics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Economics and Political Science, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - English, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Film Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - French, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - GHD, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - German, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - German Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Greek, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Hindi, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - History, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - History of Art, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Humanities, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Immuno Biology, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - INDNSN, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - International Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Italian, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Japanese, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Judaic Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Korean, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Latin, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Law School, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Linguistics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Literature, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Math, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - MCDB, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Mgt, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - MBandB, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Mbio, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Music, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Music School, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Near East, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Neuroscience, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Operations Research, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Philosophy, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Physics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Polish, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Political Science, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Portuguese, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Psychology, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Religious Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Russian and E.E., 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Russian, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Serbo-Croatian, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Science, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Sociology, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Spanish, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Special Divisional, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Statistics, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Teacher Prep, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Theater Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Yale College grade sheets, Spring 2002; Accession 2005-A-147
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Majors, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - African-American Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anthropology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Applied Math, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Applied Physics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Architecture, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Art, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Astronomy, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - British Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Child Study, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chinese, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cognitive Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - College Seminars, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Czech, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - DeVane, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Drama School, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Directed Studies (Literature), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - East Asian Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Economics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - English, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Environmental Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Film Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - French, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - German, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - German Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Greek, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - HPA (Health Public Administration), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Hindi, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - History, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - History of Art, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - HsPltcs (D.S.), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Humanities, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Indonesian, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - International Studies/Internat'l Relations, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Italian, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Japanese, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Judaic Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Korean, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Latin, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Latin American Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Law School, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Linguistics, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Literature, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Management, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Math, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - MCDB, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - MBandB, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Music, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Near East Languages, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Neuroscience, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Nursing, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Pathology, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Philosophy, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Physics, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Polish, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Political Science, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Portuguese, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Psychology, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Religious Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Russian and East European Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Russian, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Science, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Serbian and Croation, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Sociology, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Spanish, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Special Divisional, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Statistics, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Study of the City, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Teacher Prep, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Theater Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Vietnamese, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Student grade sheets, Fall 2002; Accession 2005-A-153
  - Accounting, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African and African-American Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anthropology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Applied Math, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Applied Physics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Architecture, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Art, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Astronomy, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biostatistics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cell Biology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CDE (EPH), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Child Study, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chinese, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Classics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cognitive Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - College Seminars, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Comparative Literature, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Computer Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Czech, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Directed Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Drama School, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - East Asian Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Economics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - English, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Film Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - French, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - German, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - German Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - GHD (Epidemiology and Public Health), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Greek, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Hindi, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - History, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - History of Art, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Hist. Pltcs. D.S., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Humanities, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Indonesian, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - International Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Italian, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Japanese, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Judaic Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Korean, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Latin, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Latin American Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Law School, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Linguistics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Literature, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Literature D.S., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Management, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Math, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - MCDB, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - MBandB, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Modern Greek, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Music, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Music School, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Near East Languages, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Neuroscience, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Operations Research, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Philosophy, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Philosophy (D.S.), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Physics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Polish, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Political Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Portuguese, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Psychology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Religious Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Russian and East European Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Russian, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Science, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Serbo-Croatian, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Sociology, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Spanish, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Special Divisional, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Statistics, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Teacher Prep, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Theater Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Vietnamese, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Yale College grade sheets, Spring 2003; Accession 2006-A-149
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - Major Completions, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounting, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - African American Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - African Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anthropology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Applied Math, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Applied Physics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Architecture, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Art, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Astronomy, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - British Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cell Biology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chemistry, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Child Study, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chinese, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Classic Civilizations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cognitive Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - College Seminars, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Comparative Literature, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Computer Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Czech, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - DeVane, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Directed Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Drama School, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - East Asian Langs. and Literatures., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - East Asian Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Economics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - English, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Environmental Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - EMD (Epidemiology and Public Health), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Film Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - French, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - German Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - GHD (Global Health), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Greek, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - HPA (Health Public Administration), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Hellenic Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Hindi, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - History, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - History of Art, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Humanities, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Indonesian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - International Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Italian, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Japanese, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Judaic Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Korean, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Latin, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Latin American Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Law School, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Linguistics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Literature, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Management, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Math, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Modern Greek, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - MBandB, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - MCDB, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Music, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Music School, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Near East Languages, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Operations Research, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Pathology, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Philosophy, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Physics, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Polish, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Political Science, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Portuguese, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Psychology, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Religious Studies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Renaissance Studies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Russian, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Russian and East European Studies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Science, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Serbian and Croatian, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Sociology, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Spanish, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Special Divisional, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Statistics, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Study of the City, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Teacher Prep, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Theater Studies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Vietnamese, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Yale College grade sheets, Spring 2004; Accession 2006-A-150
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2079
  - Distribution Requirements, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Major Completions, 20041 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accounting, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - African American Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - African Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anthropology, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Applied Math, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Applied Physics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arabic, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Architecture, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Art, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Astronomy, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - British Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chemistry, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Child Study, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chinese, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Classical Civilizations, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Classics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cognitive Science, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - College Seminars, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Comparative Literature, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Computer Science, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Czech, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Directed Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Drama School, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - East Asian Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Economics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Egyptian, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - English, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Environmental Engineering, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Environmental Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - EMD (Epidemiology and Public Health), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Film Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - French, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Genetics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - German Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - GHD (Global Health), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Greek, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - HPA (Health Public Administration), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Hebrew, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Hindi, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - History, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - History of Art, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Humanities, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - IBIO (Immunobiology), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Indic, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - International Relations, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - International Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Italian, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Japanese, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Korean, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Latin, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Latin American Studies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 65a)
  - Law School, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Linguistics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Literature, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Management, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Math, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - MBIO (Microbiology), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Modern Greek, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - MBandB, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - MCDB, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Music, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Music School, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Near East Languages, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Neuroscience, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Operations Research, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Pathology, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Persian, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Philosophy, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Physics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Polish, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Political Science, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Portuguese, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Psychology, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Religion, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Religious Studies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Renaissance Studies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Russian, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Russian and East European Studies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Science, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Serbian and Croatian, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Slavic Lang and Lit, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Sociology, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Spanish, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Special Divisional, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Statistics, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Study of the City, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Teacher Prep, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Theater Studies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Turkish, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Vietnamese, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Women's and Gender Studies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Yale College grade sheets, Fall 2003; Accession 2006-A-153
  - Distribution Requirements, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - World Fellows, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accounting, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - African American Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - African Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anthropology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Applied Math, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Applied Physics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arabic, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archaeological Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Architecture, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Art, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Astronomy, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - British Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cell Biology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chemical Engineering, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chemistry, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Child Study, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chinese, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CDE (Chronic Disease Epidem.), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Classics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cognitive Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - College Seminars, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Comparative Literature, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Computer Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Czech, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Directed Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Drama School, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - East Asian Langs. and Literatures., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - East Asian Studies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Economics, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)